{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"General Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40062/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40062,"taskName":"Major Home Repairs (General Contractor)","taskDescription":"Renovate or Repair a Home","xmTaskDescriptor":"General Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1702,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"addition remodel modular modern interior","textMessagingName":"General Contractor","rolloverLongDesc":"With renovations (unlike remodeling), walls, plumbing \u0026 electrical lines stay mostly where they are. This category is for substantial repairs for all or most of the home involving a mix of disciplines such as tile work, painting, flooring \u0026 plastering. Note separate categories for handyman \u0026 carpentry for less comprehensive projects.","rolloverShortDesc":"Substantial upgrades or repairs for all or most of home.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Renovate or Repair a Home.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e Home Repair Contractors | Home Repairs \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":2,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Have a variety of small projects? ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"Request a Handyman","bridgeTaskLinkId":15312,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Major Home Repairs","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Major Home Repairs (General Contractor)","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your General Contractor Need","urlName":"Major-Home-Repairs-General-Contractor","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Repair \u0026 General Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"addition, remodel, modern, renovation, renovating, home, makeover, foundation, contractor, general, repair, wall, rehab, damage, house, finish","emcCategoryOid":-12001,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":385,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40062/":{"taskOID":40062,"originalTaskOID":40062,"setID":385,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502405,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Major renovation","answerDisplayText":"Major renovation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3714,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Major home repair project","answerDisplayText":"Major home repair project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203285,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several repair projects of varying nature","answerDisplayText":"Several repair projects of varying nature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":686,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Addition to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500785,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"What type of project is this?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502406,"questionDisplayText":"Work included","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What types of work will be included in this project? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"What types of work will be included in this project? (Select all that apply)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2037,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Doors and windows","answerDisplayText":"Doors and windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4562,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Painting","answerDisplayText":"Painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2182,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Electrical","answerDisplayText":"Electrical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2624,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Framing","answerDisplayText":"Framing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5415,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roofing","answerDisplayText":"Roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1248,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Carpentry-finish","answerDisplayText":"Carpentry-finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1219,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5679,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Siding","answerDisplayText":"Siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1664,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Countertops","answerDisplayText":"Countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203286,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Deck, Porch or Patio","answerDisplayText":"Deck, Porch or Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3462,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2961,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Heating and cooling","answerDisplayText":"Heating and cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2595,"answerDisplaySequence":18,"answerText":"Foundation","answerDisplayText":"Foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":19,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":20,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502405,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Major renovation","answerDisplayText":"Major renovation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3714,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Major home repair project","answerDisplayText":"Major home repair project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203285,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several repair projects of varying nature","answerDisplayText":"Several repair projects of varying nature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":686,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Addition to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203284,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Major renovation","answerDisplayText":"Major renovation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3714,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Major home repair project","answerDisplayText":"Major home repair project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203285,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Several repair projects of varying nature","answerDisplayText":"Several repair projects of varying nature","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":686,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Addition to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500785,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"What type of project is this?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1085,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Both","answerDisplayText":"Both","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502406,"questionDisplayText":"Work included","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What types of work will be included in this project? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"What types of work will be included in this project? (Select all that apply)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2037,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Doors and windows","answerDisplayText":"Doors and windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4562,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Painting","answerDisplayText":"Painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2182,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Electrical","answerDisplayText":"Electrical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2624,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Framing","answerDisplayText":"Framing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5415,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roofing","answerDisplayText":"Roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1248,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Carpentry-finish","answerDisplayText":"Carpentry-finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1219,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5679,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Siding","answerDisplayText":"Siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1664,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Countertops","answerDisplayText":"Countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203286,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Deck, Porch or Patio","answerDisplayText":"Deck, Porch or Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3462,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2961,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Heating and cooling","answerDisplayText":"Heating and cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2595,"answerDisplaySequence":18,"answerText":"Foundation","answerDisplayText":"Foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":19,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":20,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2544,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Flooring","answerDisplayText":"Flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2037,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Doors and windows","answerDisplayText":"Doors and windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4562,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Painting","answerDisplayText":"Painting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2182,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Electrical","answerDisplayText":"Electrical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2624,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Framing","answerDisplayText":"Framing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5415,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roofing","answerDisplayText":"Roofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1248,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Carpentry-finish","answerDisplayText":"Carpentry-finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1219,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5679,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Siding","answerDisplayText":"Siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1664,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Countertops","answerDisplayText":"Countertops","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203286,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Deck, Porch or Patio","answerDisplayText":"Deck, Porch or Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2412,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Fencing","answerDisplayText":"Fencing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3462,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Landscaping","answerDisplayText":"Landscaping","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2961,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Heating and cooling","answerDisplayText":"Heating and cooling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2595,"answerDisplaySequence":18,"answerText":"Foundation","answerDisplayText":"Foundation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":19,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":20,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503473,"questionDisplayText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","shortQuestionText":"Do you need temporary storage for your home project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}